You go to Mars?
Nick has been count me out and
counting my bullets from low to
my clit.
So I'm writing down names, I'm making
a lists and checking it twice and
I'm getting them hit the real ones.
Been dying and fake losses.
Let the game is off balance.
I'm back on my shit.
The Bentley is dirty, my sneakers is
dirty. But that's how I like it.
You all are my dick, Amal and my bag.
It's hardest to get.
I do not do a powder.
I might take a sip, I might hit the
block. But I'm not about a trip.
I ain't popping no pill.
But you do as you wish.
I wrote with some things.
I love them to death.
I've got a few mail,
but not all of them.
Rich, What good is the bread of my
niggas Just go for good As far as
cleansing my niggas, that's my next
mission is why I can't quit Delilah.
I'm bringing my niggas more
chips just for the rolling right
back on my wrists.
This last game friends really gave me
a gift that went around with rain.
I just had like two letters.
Can that coexists?
But I never beef with a nigga
for nothing.
If I smoke, go Rap is coming legit.
It won't be for clout.
It won't be for fame.
It won't because my shit is
selling the same.
It won't be to sell you my
latest no sneakers.
It won't because some niggas sit
in my lane.
Everything grows is destined to
change. I love you low knickers.
I'm glad that you came.
I hope that you scrape every dollar
you paint I hope you know money.
Money raised a pain to the old G's.
I'm taking you now.
I was watching you when you was
paving the ground.
I can be joke to some average of
style.
I studied the great,
some the greatest right now. Fuck.
If you fail me,
you ain't got a choice. I do know.
Promise Still made all that noise.
The shit gonna be different.
I set my intentions.
I promise to separate out your voice.
It will tell me I'm telling my
bullies.
I'm lower my clips,
I'm writing no names.
I'm making a list and checking it
twice and I'm getting them hit the
real ones. Been dying the fake.
The game is up,
down and some big on my shit.
The bill is dirty mess niggas this
dirty but that's how I like it.
You all are my dick.
I just put something in my car.
I been want something I can
barely promise.
I have never let no money, no major.
Foot is on a mic. I got to start.
Tell me. Give me something.
They can tell a bit about this
so I don't give a fuck.
Just a young man or man in the
middle. Two generations.
I'm little Brown, big bro.
Olive was just at the level,
you know, 21 Savage.
Somebody got me chicken for lunch.
Had a long chat with the young
nigger.
Kodak reminded me a young man
straight out to project No fake
and just honest I wish that he
had more Got is for real.
Too many niggas the psychologist
spinning the birds inside of a self.
We come from a long bloodline of
trauma we raised by mama's all
we got to. Here we are in us.
This is the baby.
This is where we kill enough brothers
They poison the well distorted self
them as we said at the fair I will
make sure that the real gun purveyor.
I just put something in my cup.
I do want something I can promise.
I am never letting money open to
make Major.
But it is something that I got
to start.
I'm going to give them something
they can. Fitting boundaries.
I don't give a fuck.
Is there anyone in Omega here?
Just to make you aware.
Money your will make, Major.